[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":2670,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":5921,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure that  when we  combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":1859,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":7782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":20061,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":27846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":4454,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":32303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["6","5"],"rt":17326,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":49630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1502,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":51134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract  6 to ge t your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":9471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":60606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":7959,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":68566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5830,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":74398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6 </sub> 1  = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1031,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":75430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4408,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":79839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1173,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":81014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start  with the  first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6688,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":87703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1078,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":88782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":54488,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":143271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":3588,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":146862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":8935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":155799,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1396,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":157196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":30020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":187217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":966,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":188184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or big ger, you  subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":193543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1763,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":195307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":14323,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":209633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":20599,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":230233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":10252,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":240486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6627,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":247114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":8200,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":255316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":9581,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":264898,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4957,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":269864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1060,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":270927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3793,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":274723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1383,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":276107,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":282385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1086,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":283472,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":12945,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":296418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a  <i>gener ator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":82936,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":379358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3886,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":383247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1087,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":384335,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":387991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1271,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":389262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4  a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2408,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":391671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":886,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":392558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":395479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":879,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":396359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to co mplete t he remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":1231,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":397591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":10351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":407942,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":3639,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":411582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":415871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is  7 +<sub >9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":91842,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":507713,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":514592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4008,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":518601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5662,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":524264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5.","response_history":["5, ","5,","5."],"rt":70137,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":594402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. 8+4 is 12. 12-9 is 3","response_history":["3. 8+4 is 12. 12 ","3. 8+4 is 12. 12-9 is 3"],"rt":23524,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":617927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Anything that equals 0","response_history":["Anything that equals 0"],"rt":21943,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":639871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":10991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":650863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":11712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":662575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3006,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":665582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3+3=6 6/3=2 so the answer is 2","response_history":["3+3-","3+3=6 6/3=2 so the answer is 2"],"rt":31511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":697094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"2+2=4. 4","response_history":["2+2=4. 4/2 is 2","2+2=4. 4/2 is ","2+2=4. 4/2 is","2+2=4. 4/2 i","2+2=4. 4/2 ","2+2=4. 4/2","2+2=4. 4/","2+2=4. 4"],"rt":35024,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":732119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator  under +< sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3+3 is 6. 6 is the answer","response_history":["3+3 is 6. 6 is the answer"],"rt":14633,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":746753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5+5 is 10-9 is 1","response_history":["5+5 is 10-9 is 1"],"rt":15165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":761919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I dont know.","response_history":["I dont know."],"rt":115690,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":877610,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":2044,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":879655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":15431,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":895087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got  your ans wer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+n=xn","response_history":["x+n=xn"],"rt":11823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":906911,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i dont remember ","response_history":["i dont remeber ","i dont remember "],"rt":47784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":954696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":5665,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":960361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":2488,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":962850,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":5598,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":968450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explai n in wor ds why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False, i'm guessing. I am really confused now","response_history":["False, i'm guessing. I am really confused now"],"rt":56338,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1024790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":8039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1032831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Guessing, Confused","response_history":["Guessing, Confused"],"rt":13095,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1045927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":4352,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1050280,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1582,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1051863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"23","response_history":["23"],"rt":2344,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1054207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","response_history":["Associates Degree"],"rt":2560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1056768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"AP Statis tics ","response_history":["AP Statisics ","AP Statistics "],"rt":12606,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1069375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":7559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1076935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or r ecently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":4760,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1081696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1084975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2615,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1087591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":1982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1089575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1091256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6119,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1097375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3936,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1101311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":808,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1102119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]